acunetix.com 2019-11-16

# Privacy Policy | Acunetix

## Privacy Statement

Acunetix (“We”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy, which includes any items of personal data, which altogether could constitute the Personal Information that you may choose to provide to us (“Personal Information”).

This policy (together with our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.acunetix.com/company/terms_conditions/)) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting acunetix.com, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.

We will process all your Personal Information in accordance with the applicable data protection law.

## Introduction

Our goal is to provide you with a personalized internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. In order to achieve this goal, we sometimes collect information during your visits to understand what differentiates you from each of our millions of other users, and we may also ask you for Personal Information that enables us to give you access to some parts of our web site. We will not disclose your information to any person outside our organization except as described in this Privacy Policy.

To demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have prepared this statement disclosing our privacy practices. This statement describes what personal identifying information is collected, how and when we might use your information, how we protect your information, who has access to your information, and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

## Information We Receive

We collect certain information from and about our visitors in four ways: from our web server logs, using cookies, with the assistance of third party marketing technologies provided by reputable service providers or vendors, and directly from you.

### Web Server Logs

When you visit our website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. With each visit we may automatically collect the following information:

  * **Technical information** , including the internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform.
  * **Information about your visit** , including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), methods used to browse away from the page, and any phone number used to call our customer service number.

### Cookies

Cookies are small text files stored on your computer by your browser. They are used for many things, such as remembering whether you’ve visited the site before, so that you remain logged in or to help us work out how many new website visitors we get each month. Cookies do not include Personal Information about you, they cannot harm your computer, and do not contain any viruses.

Acunetix uses cookies to improve your experience on this site. We would like to let you know a few things about our cookies:

  * Certain cookies are essential to the proper function of this site
  * We do not track your personal activities when you’re not on this site
  * We use analytics cookies to help us understand what content is most useful to our visitors

**Types of Cookies**

  * Analytics cookies: We track site traffic patterns to identify popular site content and potential site problems
  * We also use cookies to split some users into test groups to test new site features

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being set, or you can choose to turn off all cookies; you do this through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you will not have access to many features that make your experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. Blocking or deleting cookies from the site may prevent you from using the site.

### Third-Party Technologies

We use Google services (Analytics, Remarketing, Display). You can read about how Google uses data when you use our sites or apps [here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). We use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the internet. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party and third-party cookies together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on a person’s past visits to our website. You are able to opt out from all this [here](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

### Information We Receive from You

Visitors can register or fill out the necessary forms to obtain access to some parts of our website (including but not limited to download pages, online service pages, blog to email services, partner portal, shopping cart). We will ask you for some Personal Information or information related to your role in the organization you represent. Some of the information requested will be required for registration or transaction and some may be optional. Also, we may ask you to disclose further Personal Information to enable us to provide assistance and information to you. We may also collect and process data about you to help in administrative purposes. You may give us personal _i_ nformation by filling in the registration/download form on our website acunetix.com or by sending other documentation. The Personal Information that you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, and other relevant information.

### Other Information Supplied by You

Any information submitted to us as part of a support issue will only be made available to us.

## Use of Your Personal Information

We will use the information you give to us to:

  * Carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information that you request from us
  * Ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer

We will use the Personal Information that we collect about you to:

  * Administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes
  * Improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer
  * As part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure

## Sharing of Identifiable Information

We will share your Personal Information as required by law or by the order of any competent court or (semi-)governmental authority or in matters of public safety or policy. Under strict conditions of confidentiality, we may share your Personal Information with agents and contractors who use it on our behalf or in connection with their relationship with us. We will also share your Personal Information as may be needed in connection with the enforcement of agreements.

## Anonymous Information

We may provide summary statistics about our interests and preferences of visitors to our web site, traffic patterns, and related site information. These statistics do not include personally identifiable information.

## Security Measures

We use technical security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control and information about our subscribers and their web site usage is maintained in a secure environment. Information about our subscribers and their web site usage is not shared with third parties for marketing purposes. We do not disclose any information about any subscriber’s usage of our web site except in specific cases, and we do not share information with any unaffiliated third parties for marketing purposes unless you expressly give us permission to do so.

## Where We Store Your Data

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

All Personal Information that you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password, which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share the password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.

## Access to Your Information

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act by sending an email to [privacy@acunetix.com](mailto:privacy@acunetix.com)

## Promotional Messages

If you don’t want to receive promotional materials from us, you can opt-out at any time by sending an email to [privacy@acunetix.com](mailto:privacy@acunetix.com).

## Privacy Policy Changes

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Privacy Policy on this page. It is your responsibility to check this page periodically for any updates.

## Contact

Questions, comments, and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [privacy@acunetix.com](mailto:privacy@acunetix.com).

_This Privacy Policy has last been updated on 18 May 2018._
